<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
	<content-type>/page/generic</content-type>	<display-template>/templates/web/generic.ftl</display-template>
	<merge-strategy>inherit-levels</merge-strategy>
	<objectGroupId>d251</objectGroupId>
	<objectId>d2513579-4832-07dc-83be-5ae55b991555</objectId>
	<internal-name>About</internal-name>
	<navLabel>About</navLabel>
	<placeInNav>true</placeInNav>
	<file-name>index.xml</file-name>
	<folder-name>about-us</folder-name>
	<body>&lt;p&gt;Rosies Rivet&amp;#39;s was founded in 2003 by industry veteran Jeffrey Lubell. The founder, chairman and chief executive officer built the brand based on the principles of quality, American-made authentic denim with timeless appeal and a vintage aesthetic. The brand offers a wide range of styles in nearly every category and embraces the motto: "It&amp;rsquo;s all about the fit." Rosies Rivet&amp;#39;s clothing is made for and by people who don&amp;#39;t follow trends, they set them.The story of how Rosies Rivet&amp;#39;s came to be is a uniquely American tale. As a teenager growing up in New York, Lubell would bleach bell-bottoms and embellish his favorite pairs of jeans with leather and denim patches when they became ripped and worn. He also drew album covers on jackets and added hand-embroidered finishes. "This is where my denim journey began," he says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lubell bet everything on his vision as a designer and entrepreneur. This marked a new era for the innovator, who started Rosies Rivet&amp;#39;s at the sewing machine. He established trendsetting elements such as thicker threads in a multitude of colors, lock seams and customization of oversized hardware in a variety of novelty styles for both men and women. As for the name? "There&amp;#39;s only one real religion and that&amp;#39;s people," says Lubell. "And all the people in the world wear jeans. Our emphasis is on fit, quality and style and the inspiration to make men and women look and feel good in their jeans."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;All the people in the world wear jeans. Our emphasis is on fit, quality and style and the inspiration to make men and women look and feel good in their jeans.&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lubell&amp;#39;s faith in his new company was tested early on. He determinedly won over a skeptical buyer to have his first order placed at an L.A.-based specialty store. He also gifted pairs to the sales staff, knowing that his now signature creations looked better on a body than on a shelf. The remaining pairs sold out within two days, and Rosies Rivet&amp;#39;s had found its believers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having launched with denim offerings for both men and women, it was the undeniable great fit, style and comfort that eventually won over the population. The jeans were unique and allowed enthusiasts to express their individuality. The "Joey" jean became (and still is) the cult favorite across both categories with its twisted asymmetrical seams, colorful reinforced stitching and oversized low flap pockets. It was an instant favorite for everyone from fashionable stay-at-home moms to uber-celebrities such as Angelina Jolie, Jessica Simpson, Megan Fox, Kate Hudson and Jennifer Lopez as well as a myriad of stylish male stars.&lt;/p&gt;</body>
	<createdDate>05/17/2013 01:31:52</createdDate>
	<lastModifiedDate>5/12/2015 21:17:46</lastModifiedDate>
	<author>Ella Smith</author>
	<disabled>false</disabled>
	<headline>About Rosie's Rivets 123</headline>
	<orderDefault_f>18000</orderDefault_f>
	<rteComponents>	<item>	<id>d71ea903-beca-2ae9-f3b5-8f15647a1f0c</id>
	<contentId>/site/components/d71ea903-beca-2ae9-f3b5-8f15647a1f0c.xml</contentId>
	<include>/site/components/d71ea903-beca-2ae9-f3b5-8f15647a1f0c.xml</include>
	</item></rteComponents>
	<campaigns/>
</page>